<resources>
    <string name="app_name">New Town High</string>
    <string name="app_email">new.town.high@education.tas.gov.au</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="home_text">
        "Welcome to New Town High School. We are a Tasmanian Government secondary school for boys located in New Town, a leafy inner suburb of Hobart,"
        "Tasmania, Australia. Picturesque and spacious grounds, strong traditions and demanding academic programs in the core learning areas of Mathematics,"
        "English, Science, and History result in strong enrollment demand. The School has a reputation for its specialist Music programs, and provides a challenging"
        "curriculum and up to date facilities in Technology, Computing, the Visual Arts, and Health and Physical Education. A contemporary program in Food Studies,"
        "a vibrant Languages other than English program, and a comprehensive range of activities in the Performing Arts ensure that boys have access to a diverse"
        "and rich range of educational experiences."\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_about_screen">About New Town High</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        \n"As the only all boys Government high school in Tasmania, we provide our students with a high quality education that is facilitated through a caring and"
        "supportive school environment. We acknowledge and cater for the differentiated needs and talents of each and every boy in our care. New Town High School"
        "prepares students for further and continuing education, for future employment and to be positive members of a democratic society. We endeavor to develop"
        "boys of resilient and respectful character who can lead fulfilling and productive lives within our increasingly globalised and technologically advanced society."

        \n\n"Our school provides first class learning activities in the fields of academic study, health and physical education, social development, cultural pursuits and special"
        "interest programs. This commitment is met through the structures of the curriculum and through the creation of a positive and supportive learning environment"
        "in which boys are challenged to maximise their educational opportunities. Our teaching teams are engaged in continuous cycles of professional inquiry that"
        "foster ongoing professional development in our pursuit of teaching excellence."

        \n\n"Parents choose New Town High School for their sons’ secondary education for a variety of reasons. We celebrate a proud heritage with a strong professional"
        "reputation which has been developed through family association, valued traditions, excellence in teaching and learning, sport, international opportunity and"
        "extra curricula activities."

        \n\n"Our timeless and ever relevant motto, ‘We Build for the Future’ highlights the forward thinking nature of the programs that we offer. Our motto, vision, mission"
        "and core values statements guide our strategic directions and influence our professional decision making processes.\nWe embed our finest traditions and"
        "professional heritage as <b><i>We Build For The Future.</i></b>"\n\n

        <b>"Jason Szczerbanik,"</b>
        \n<b>"PRINCIPAL"</b>\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_plan_screen">Strategic Plan</string>
    <string name="plan_text">
        \n<b>"OUR VISION"</b>
        \n"To embed our finest traditions and heritage as We Build For The Future."

        \n\n<b>"OUR MISSION"</b>
        \n"To develop boys of resilient and respectful character who can lead fulfilling and productive lives within our increasingly globalised and technologically advanced society."

        \n\n<b>"OUR STRATEGIC PRIORITIES"</b>
        \n"– Excellence in Teaching, Learning and Curriculum Implementation"
        \n"– Supportive School Environment"
        \n"– Efficient, Practical and Legally Accountable School Administration"

        \n\n<b>"OUR CORE VALUES"</b>
        \n"– Equity: We have high expectations for our learners and a strong commitment to the pursuit of excellence and innovation in our staff, in our Programs"
        "and learning environments."
        \n"– Respect: We all have the right to access challenging and engaging learning opportunities in appropriate settings."
        \n"– Relationships: Positive and effective interactions with each other and within our environment are conducted on the basis of responsibility, integrity"
        "and accountability."
        \n"– Excellence: We achieve growth and strength through partnerships and connections with our colleagues, students and our community."

        \n\n<b>"OUR KEY DRIVERS"</b>
        \n"– Successful Learners: We empower students to set a high expectation for their lifelong learning and to achieve their potential through expert teaching."
        \n"– Critical and Creative Thinking: We use cycles of data informed professional inquiry to critically reflect upon our professional practices. We use collaborative"
        "dialogue and professional networks to develop and amplify innovative ideas throughout our organisation."
        \n"– A Highly Skilled Teaching and Administrative Team: Our teaching and administrative team are the most influential factors that affect our capacity to produce"
        "optimal Student Outcomes."
        "– A Globalised and Technologically Advanced World: We monitor and adapt to the rapidly changing globalised environment. We are a dynamic and innovative Learning"
        "Organisation"\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
